gamerage.com 2014-11-24

# GameRage – Home of Free Online Games – Get Fired Up!

* Our Privacy Commitment

SMILEGATE EUROPE. ("SGE," "we," "us" or "our") is committed to respecting the privacy rights and concerns of all users of the SGE websites where this Privacy Policy is posted (the "Site(s)") (we refer to the Site(s), the services and the online videogames made available through the Site(s), collectively, as the "SGE Features"). As such, we have established and implemented this Privacy Policy to inform visitors to the Site(s) and users of the SGE Features how we use and protect the information we collect through the Site(s). By visiting the Site(s) or using any of the SGE Features, you consent to SGE's collection, use, storage, deletion and disclosure of information relating to you as set forth in this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is effective as of the date set forth above and is only applicable to the Site(s) and not to any other website that you may be able to access from the Site(s) which may have its own data collection and use practices and policies.

* European Union and Switzerland"s Directive on Data Protection - Safe Harbor

SGE complies with the U.S.-EU Safe Harbor Framework and the U.S.-Swiss Safe Harbor Framework as set forth by the U.S. Department of Commerce regarding the collection, use, and retention of personal information from European Union member countries and Switzerland. SGE has certified that it adheres to the Safe Harbor Privacy Principles of notice, choice, onward transfer, security, data integrity, access, and enforcement. To learn more about the Safe Harbor program, and to view SGE's certification, please visit http://www.export.gov/safeharbor.

This policy answers the following questions:

• What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?  
• Will we share your personal information with third parties?  
• What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?  
• What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

* What information do we collect about you and how do we use it?

**Types of Information We Collect**

Personal information means information that can be used to identify and contact you. You do not need to submit personal information to access certain areas of the Site(s), but if you do not want to disclose certain personal information to us, you will not be able to access certain aspects of the SGE Features.

We collect personal information when you create an account through the SGE Features; subscribe to our newsletter; participate in polls, surveys, and questionnaires; participate in contests, sweepstakes, or other promotions; purchase a product through the SGE Features; register a product that you have purchased; or receive customer or technical support.

To create an account for the SGE Features, we require you to provide your name, date of birth and email address. When you are purchasing products through the SGE Features, in addition to your name, e-mail address and screen name that you choose, we will ask for your shipping and billing address, telephone number, credit card or other payment information.

Additionally, we may also collect other types of information (known as demographic information) such as your gender, hobbies, occupation, platform preferences, and other game ownership information. This demographic information may be associated with your personal information. 

**How We Use Your Personal Information**

The personal information you provide to us will allow us to fulfill your product or service order; alert you of new products or services, features, or enhancements; handle/route your customer service questions or issues; and/or notify you of upgrade opportunities, contests, promotions, or special events and offers. We also use your e-mail address to send you messages about the Site(s) and other general announcements. We keep track of your interactions with us, including but not limited to your activity within the SGE Features. We may use personal information that you provide to us to send messages to you in response to your request to perform an activity in connection with your use of any of the SGE Features. We may also use your personal information to contact you when necessary. 

**Cookies**

"Cookies" are small bits of electronic information that a website sends to a visitor"s browser and are stored on the visitor"s hard drive. Like many websites, we may employ cookies in certain areas of the Site(s) to allow us to provide information which is targeted to your interests and to make your online experience more convenient. Additionally, advertisements that are managed by third parties which may appear on the Site(s) use cookies. Advertisers use cookies to collect non-personal information when you click on or move your cursor over one of their banner advertisements. You may not realize this information is being collected. Advertisers use this information to monitor the performance of their advertisements. In some cases, we may have access to information from cookies used by these advertisers on the Site(s) and this information may permit us to identify other sites that you have visited that are also associated such advertisers. 

**Log Information**

Our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit the Site(s). This information includes your Internet Protocol address, your browser type and version, the search engine you used to find the SGE Features, if any, the operating system your computer uses, which SGE Features you use and when and how long you use them. We use this information to monitor and analyze how users use the SGE Features, to provide customer service and to maintain and improve the SGE Features. 

**Children"s Privacy**

We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13. We take children"s privacy seriously, and encourage parents to play an active role in their children"s online experience at all times. 

**Business Information**

Please note that we treat personal information submitted to us in a business capacity different from information we receive in a non-business capacity. Personal information submitted to us in a business capacity (e.g. resumes, event sponsorship, etc.) is not subject to this Privacy Policy. 

* Will we share your personal information with third parties?

**Sharing of Information**

We may use your personal information to provide analyses of our users in the aggregate to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties. We may also disclose and otherwise use, on an anonymous basis, affiliation, position, interests and other non-personal information about customers. 

In addition, we will share the personal information we collect from you under the following circumstances: 

Protection of rights. We will share personal information if we have a good faith belief that (i) access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process, such as a court order or subpoena, or a request by law enforcement or governmental authorities, (ii) such action is appropriate to enforce the Terms of Use for the SGE Features, including any investigation of potential violations thereof, (iii) such action is necessary to detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues associated with the SGE Features, or (iv) such action is appropriate to protect the rights, property or safety of SGE , its employees, users of the SGE Features or others. 

Asset transfers. If we become involved in a merger, acquisition or other transaction involving the sale of some or all of SGE's assets, user information, including personal information collected from you through your use of the SGE Features, could be included in the transferred assets. Visitors to the Site(s) will be notified via a prominent notice on the Site(s) for thirty (30) days prior to a change of ownership or control of user information held by us. 

Service Providers. We may share your personal information with service providers that we engage for the purpose of processing information on our and your behalf. For example, we may partner with other companies to maintain or manage the SGE Features and our online videogames, process consumer surveys, fulfill product orders or prizes, process payments, or to process, analyze, and/or store data. While providing services for us, these companies may access your personal information. We require these entities to comply with this Privacy Policy and appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 

**Additional Information You Should Know About Third Parties**

This Privacy Policy applies only to the SGE Features maintained by SGE, and not to our international affiliates, or any websites or online videogames maintained by them. 

Additionally, this Privacy Policy does not cover the information practices of third party websites linked to the Site(s). Although we encourage such third parties to adopt and follow their own privacy policies, we are not responsible for their collection and use of your personal information. You should refer to the privacy policies and statements of other websites or contact the respective webmasters of those websites to obtain information regarding their information collection, use and disclosure policies. 

When you have clicked on an advertisement or third party logo displayed on our Site(s) which links you to a different website, our Privacy Policy no longer applies and you must read the privacy policy of the advertiser to see how your personal information will be handled on their website. 

The SGE Features may also have message boards and/or chat areas, where users can exchange ideas and communicate with one another. When you post to a message board or chat area, please be aware that the information you post is made publicly available on-line and you do so at your own risk. 

* What choices do you have about the collection and use of your personal information?

**Control of Your Information**

You may update or delete your personal information or modify your account preferences for the SGE Features by accessing the "My Account" area of the SGE Features. Please note that when you delete your account, we may retain your account information for a reasonable period of time afterward for the purpose of internal account management and fraud prevention activities. 

**Opting Out of Receiving Communications from Us**

If you no longer want to receive our newsletter, e-mails or other announcements, you may unsubscribe by selecting "unsubscribe" in your account or writing to us at [customer.support@gamerage.com](mailto:customer.support@gamerage.com). Please note that you cannot unsubscribe from certain correspondence from us, including messages relating to your account transactions. 

**Mediation**

You also agree that, in the event any dispute or claim arises out of or relating to your use of the Site(s) or the SGE Features or this Privacy Policy that you and SGE will attempt in good faith to negotiate a written resolution of the matter directly between the parties. You agree that if the matter remains unresolved for forty-five (45) days after notification (via certified mail or personal delivery) that a dispute exists, all parties shall join in mediation services in Orange County, California with a mutually agreed mediator in an attempt to resolve the dispute. Should you file any arbitration claims, or any administrative or legal actions without first having attempted to resolve the matter by mediation, then you agree that you will not be entitled to recover attorney's fees, even if you would otherwise be entitled to them.

* What security measures do we take to safeguard your personal information?

The personal information that you provide to us is stored on servers, which are located in secured facilities with restricted access, and protected by protocols and procedures designed to ensure the security of such information. In addition, we restrict access to personal information to SGE employees, independent contractors and agents who need to know this information in order to develop, operate and maintain the SGE Features. All SGE personnel who have access to this information are trained in the maintenance and security of such information. However, no server, computer or communications network or system, or data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect user information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us or through the use of any of the SGE Features and you acknowledge and agree that you provide such information and engage in such transmissions at your own risk. Once we receive a transmission from you, we will endeavor to maintain its security on our systems.

* Notification of Changes

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time and we will post all changes on this page.

* Questions? Contact Us

If you have any questions about our privacy practices or this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at [customer.support@gamerage.com](mailto:customer.support@gamerage.com).

* Terms of Use

Please read the Terms of Use governing the use of the Site(s) and the SGE Features.
